July 18, 2022.
We'll have the implication of our entire pastor, first-class church, Mr. Lee, on lease.
Would it be disrespectful to have special prayer for Robert first?
Absolutely not.
That will stop recording and start recording.
Lord, thank you that we've all have been the last of you.
Good Father, I thank you for this one who makes decisions.
Give them special assistance.
Father, bless the work of the state.
Ladies and gentlemen, it's two to the five of the United States of America.
And we'll see the three of you out of the Croatia state's one nation under the law.
In the end it is a little bit different from the United States of this world.
Four of the Republican booths are on schedule personal appearances.
And then five consent agenda staff recommend that you brew on six and seven.
Take a motion to a brew?
Thank you.
He's dead.
Hi.
Do you call him?
Davis.
Hi.
Silver.
Parker.
Eight.
Table of the agenda item from July 5, 2022 meeting.
The Davis right for meeting.
Colleen for Pensacled and Jardier.
Realizing seeing in the amount of 33,510 dollars.
So, during our last meeting, it was suggested that we put together more of a brief description.
So, we've got a couple of the works that had been performed on that particular invoice.
So, what we've included in your packets this time is a BA that's got some background in there.
Kind of really is our summation because we get a detailed description of all the hours before we work before.
And so, we've summarized that in there.
Hopefully that better meets the expectations of the council and gives you all a very good idea of the type of,
of the type of work and what work was performed during that period.
And this will become a new norm that will write these up each time we have one of those invoices.
Because I realize it's important to understand how that litigating spin and what the attorneys are actually doing.
I appreciate the feedback and the happy answer any questions you all have.
Thank you for doing this.
I know it was me that asked for the more detail and I just feel more comfortable being able to speak.
Being able to speak to this if it's, you know, if I'm question on the street or in a phone.
call, you know, instead of just a dollar figure.
So I appreciate that.
Thank you.
Happy to do it.
If you all ever have any thoughts with feedback on it,
or something else, you want to see it.
And I want to hear that last meeting.
So I'd appreciate it as well, because not only can we see it,
the public can see it if they need to come and look at it.
So yeah, absolutely.
And that was kind of what we had in mind
was making sure that we provided enough explanation.
The general population could read it and understand
what work was being done.
I'll make a motion.
We approve.
Hi.
Davis.
Don't call.
Hi.
Son Merck.
Hey.
Parker.
Hi.
Number nine.
You're the L. Stratton Edmunds and Palmer.
L. C. Klienfer, Pensacola, Jardier,
relaxing seeing the amount of $5,716.37.
So like the previous item, but this one was not on the previous council.
So this is a new one that came in since then, but we took the opportunity.
To apply the same methodology and write up a better description
for the council and for the public.
Second.
Hi.
Davis.
Second.
Parker.
10.
Award bid C. 22.
That's 15A contract.
We're state highway 69A and 10.
Waterline relocation amount of $331,000.
Sean Conneigh.
That's it.
So this is for utility conflicts with the amount of intersection project.
It's going on out there at the 10 and 16.
Everything's in easements.
So it's an hour and a centering burst through it up.
The contract to circle B.
So it's just going to be going out.
Then we'll get it right back.
What does this work?
Must start.
Need to get these moves.
So that's going to start.
So when you get going.
I'm hoping it will start here in the next month.
Second.
Dr. Circle B, they said too much.
Well, that cost, let's do the movie that you tell us about.
Well, that cost some road closures and stuff out that way.
No, we're going to do all those two existing line lines there.
There's a raw water from the material, both of them back in.
It's a plain same place right next to it.
So it's start to finish for two months.
And once this money goes out, how long does it take for us to get it back from, oh no.
I'm not, he's down the reimbursement on the other projects.
So, I'm going to tell you more questions.
I'll make a motion to approve.
Bye.
All right.
Now, let them award CC-16A contract for State Highway 6 on A&TM,
Sanctuary, sewer relocation in the amount of $216,000.
Let's be the same thing.
Same company.
There will be a warden.
And same thing.
This two 16 will be reimbursed.
Yeah, what in row?
There wasn't even a row there.
Yeah.
That row used to dead in, right past that farmhouse in front of Buffalo Run, right?
No, you see all the way to the 90 I think, and you can turn to college farm.
Oh, thank you.
Everybody was dirt road.
It was dirt road.
Yeah.
Yes.
Davis.
All right.
Sanctuary.
There won't be.
All right.
Thanks, Sean.
12.
Other new business of any, which is resistance in the posting of this agenda.
13 staff reports, 14 trusty community announcements, 15 and adjournment.
So, move.
Is that fun?